<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Build by Tony Fadell on Fernando's Hub</title><link>https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/</link><description>Recent content in Build by Tony Fadell on Fernando's Hub</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ideation as a Muscle: Training Your Mind to Generate Great Ideas</title><link>https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/ideation_training/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 00:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/ideation_training/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="understanding-our-goals-developing-a-process-and-trusting-the-journey">Understanding Our Goals, Developing a Process, and Trusting the Journey&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;A company that’s likely to make a substantial change in the status quo &amp;hellip; is thinking about a problem or a customer need in a way you’ve never heard before, but which makes perfect sense once you hear it.&amp;quot;&lt;p>
—&lt;strong>Tony Fadell&lt;/strong>, &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/59696349-build" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Build&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;h4 id="why-understand-our-goal-for-ideation">&lt;strong>Why&lt;/strong>: Understand Our Goal for Ideation&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Ideation is a muscle that we must train, similar to how we exercise our bodies to become stronger and healthier. Good ideas don&amp;rsquo;t simply come out of the blue or happen by chance. They are a result of consistent effort and practice. By generating multiple ideas and discerning whether they are good or bad, we can identify the necessary features for successful ideas and refine our ideation skills. This continuous exercise helps us build a strong foundation for innovation and creativity, enabling us to tackle challenges, seize opportunities with confidence, and frame solutions to problems in creative ways.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Art of Doing, Failing, and Learning</title><link>https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/the_art_of_doing_failing_and_learning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:00:00 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://f-yanez.github.io/posts/build/the_art_of_doing_failing_and_learning/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="navigating-lifes-cycles-embracing-change-and-learning">Navigating Life&amp;rsquo;s Cycles: Embracing Change and Learning&lt;/h3>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>&amp;ldquo;Adulthood is your opportunity to screw up continually until you learn how to screw up a little bit less. (&amp;hellip;) Do, fail, learn. The rest will follow.&amp;quot;&lt;p>
—&lt;strong>Tony Fadell&lt;/strong>, &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/59696349-build" target="_blank" rel="noopener">Build&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>Over the past decade, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize that my life has been a series of cycles: not knowing what I&amp;rsquo;m doing, choosing a reasonable next step, advancing as much as possible, noticing things aren&amp;rsquo;t entirely right, and starting again. The important aspect of these cycles is the presence of constants: my vision for my future and my values. These guiding principles help me evaluate options, seek advice, and make decisions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>